const STORE = [
    {
      question: 'Fort Worth is in the top 20 biggest cities in the U.S., where do they rank?',
      answer: [
        '13th largest',
        '7th largest',
        '15th largest',
        '10th largest'
        ],
      correctAnswer: '13th largest'
    },

    {
      question: 'Which one of the following is not a nickname of Fort Worth?',
      answer: [
        'Cowtown',
        'Longhorn City',
        'Funkytown',
        'Panther City'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Longhorn City'
    },

    {
      question: 'Fort Worth is also one of the biggest cities in Texas, where do they rank?',
      answer: [
        '6th biggest',
        '2nd biggest',
        '4th biggest',
        '5th biggest'    
        ],
      correctAnswer: '5th biggest'
    },

    {
      question: 'Fort Worth is known for its hot summers, the highest temperature ever recorded was:',
      answer: [
        '104 degrees',
        '110 degrees',
        '113 degrees',
        '119 degrees'
        ],
      correctAnswer: '113 degrees'
    },

    {
      question: 'The Fort Worth Zoo was the first zoo to open in the state of Texas, which year did it open?',
      answer: [
        '1934',
        '1918',
        '1927',
        '1909'
        ],
      correctAnswer: '1909'
    },

    {
      question: 'One of our presidents gave their last speech in Fort Worth before being assasinated, which president was it?',
      answer: [
        'James A. Garfield',
        'John F. Kennedy',
        'William McKinley',
        'Abraham Lincoln'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'John F. Kennedy'
    },

    {
      question: 'Which famous pop artist was born in Fort Worth?',    
      answer: [
        'Brittany Spears',
        'Carrie Underwood',
        'Kelly Clarkson',
        'Taylor Swift'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Kelly Clarkson'
    },

    {
      question: 'Which one of the following Fort Worth facts is False?',
      answer: [
        'It is home to the largest honky-tonk in the world',
        'It has the worldâ€™s only twice a day cattle drive',
        'They have five world-class museums',
        'It is home to the University of Texas'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'It is home to the University of Texas'
    },

    {
      question: 'Fort Worth is part of the DFW Metroplex which is one of the largest in the U.S., where does it rank?',
      answer: [
        '2nd largest',
        '4th largest',
        '5th largest',
        '7th largest'
        ],
     correctAnswer: '4th largest'
    },

    {
      question: 'Which animal is set a top police department badges in Fort Worth?',
      answer: [
        'A longhorn', 
        'A bull', 
        'A panther',
        'A rattlesnake' 
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'A panther'
    },
];